<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Woodshed Agency Thoughts]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Woodshed Agency Thoughts]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 17:47:08 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="undefinedrss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[7 Essential Habits to Become a Healthy Entrepreneur]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>7 Essential Habits to Become a Healthy Entrepreneur</h1><p>Over the last three months, I have been struggling with a major problem in my life: my personal health. To put a finer point on that statement, my health when it comes to being an entrepreneur,  husband, and dad of two small kids. It’s no secret that in the last decade I’ve gained a few pounds, lost some great hair, and found that my dad’s anger and rage has officially been passed down. Mentally I’ve struggled with, “How can I be a leader for my team as well as my family and not give a shit about my health?" It just doesn’t line up. So back in late October when I was sitting at my dinner table with Shawn and Paul discussing our plans for a new kind of digital agency, I was also thinking about how I wanted my health to be a part of all these new conversations.  So January 1st of this year, when the three of us launched theWoodshed Agency, I also went to work carving official time out for ME—something I have not done in the last decade.  Here were my first two steps.First I joined Bikram Yoga. I’m proud to say I’m on week 3, and I’ve been attending three classes a week. I took the time to research an exercise program and found I love a ton of the philosophies of Bikram Yoga.Second step:The food that goes into my body. I joined Blue Apron. Now my wife and I get three vegetarian meals delivered each week that I cook and prepare for us. The food is fresh and organic, and the recipes are ones that I would never think of myself. I've also completely cut carbonated sodas out of my diet, and I’m knocking down gallons of water a day for cleansing.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/069acd4c3f106475be3dba31ac5a1bcb94b31a80.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>undefined7-essential-habits-to-become-a-healthy-entrepreneur/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f3d53112-d311-49cf-9392-ada7c6c756bc</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 17:47:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>